the-digital-reader.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | The Digital Reader

The Digital Reader operates the-digital-reader.com and other websites. It is The Digital Reader’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, The Digital Reader collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

The Digital Reader’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how The Digital Reader’s visitors use its website. From time to time, The Digital Reader may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website, or by sharing your deepest darkest secrets with your worst enemies.

The Digital Reader also collects potentially personally-identifying information like your aura, retinal scan, blood sample, or your Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on The Digital Reader.

The Digital Reader only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to The Digital Reader’s websites choose to interact with The Digital Reader in ways that require The Digital Reader to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that The Digital Reader gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at The Digital Reader to provide a username and email address.

Those who engage in transactions with The Digital Reader are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, The Digital Reader collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with The Digital Reader. The Digital Reader does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## Aggregated Statistics

The Digital Reader may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. What The Digital Reader does with this data in the darkness of our broom closet is our business. However, The Digital Reader does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

The Digital Reader discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on The Digital Reader’s behalf or to provide services available at The Digital Reader’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using The Digital Reader’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

The Digital Reader will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, The Digital Reader discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when The Digital Reader believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of The Digital Reader, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of The Digital Reader  and have supplied your email address, The Digital Reader may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with The Digital Reader and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. The Digital Reader takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Cookies

We like cookies, including chocolate chip, raisin dashes, and thin mints. Here’s my secret recipe for chocolate chip cookies:

  * 1 cup white sugar
  * 1 cup dark brown sugar
  * 3/4 cup shortening
  * 3/4 cup butter
  * 2 eggs
  * 1 teaspoon salt
  * 1 teaspoon baking soda
  * 1 teaspoon vanilla
  * 2 and 1/2 cups flour
  * 2 12-ounce bags of chocolate chips

Mix the first five (5) ingredients in a 2-quart bowl until it is mostly consistent, then add the salt, vanilla, and baking soda. Continue to mix, and then add the flour. Continue to mix the batter, and occasionally use a spatula to clean the sides of the bowl so all the ingredients are mixed in evenly. Then mix in as many or as few chocolate chips as you like. Form into balls, and then place then on a cookie sheet and bake at 350 degrees to 400 degrees Fahrenheit.

Our website also likes cookies.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Digital Reader uses cookies to help The Digital Reader identify and track visitors, their usage of The Digital Reader website, and their website access preferences. The Digital Reader visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using The Digital Reader’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of The Digital Reader’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If The Digital Reader, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that The Digital Reader goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of The Digital Reader may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies, harvest your soul, or visit your house to give your children puppies and candy. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by The Digital Reader and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, The Digital Reader may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in The Digital Reader’s sole discretion. The Digital Reader encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a The-Digital-Reader.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact

The Digital Reader can be reached by email at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or via the mailing address below:

The Digital Reader  
13884 Montoclair Ln  
Dale City VA 22013
